{"test_questions": [[{"question": "Every time attribute A appears, it is matched with the same value of attribute B, but not the same value of attribute C. Therefore, it is true that:", "opta": "A \u2192 B.", "optb": "A \u2192 C.", "optc": "A \u2192 (B,C).", "optd": "(B,C) \u2192 A.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The different classes of relations created by the technique for preventing modification anomalies are called:", "opta": "normal forms.", "optb": "referential integrity constraints.", "optc": "functional dependencies.", "optd": "None of the above is correct.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A relation is in this form if it is in BCNF and has no multivalued dependencies:", "opta": "second normal form.", "optb": "third normal form.", "optc": "fourth normal form.", "optd": "domain/key normal form.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Row is synonymous with the term:", "opta": "record.", "optb": "relation.", "optc": "column.", "optd": "field.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "The primary key is selected from the:", "opta": "composite keys.", "optb": "determinants.", "optc": "candidate keys.", "optd": "foreign keys.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is a group of one or more attributes that uniquely identifies a row?", "opta": "Key", "optb": "Determinant", "optc": "Tuple", "optd": "Relation", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "When the values in one or more attributes being used as a foreign key must exist in another set of one or more attributes in another table, we have created a(n):", "opta": "transitive dependency.", "optb": "insertion anomaly.", "optc": "referential integrity constraint.", "optd": "normal form.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A relation is considered a:", "opta": "Column.", "optb": "one-dimensional table.", "optc": "two-dimensional table.", "optd": "three-dimensional table.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "In the relational model, relationships between relations or tables are created by using:", "opta": "composite keys.", "optb": "determinants.", "optc": "candidate keys.", "optd": "foreign keys.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A functional dependency is a relationship between or among:", "opta": "tables.", "optb": "rows.", "optc": "relations.", "optd": "attributes.", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Table is synonymous with the term:", "opta": "record.", "optb": "relation.", "optc": "column.", "optd": "field.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "Which of the following is not a restriction for a table to be a relation?", "opta": "The cells of the table must contain a single value.", "optb": "All of the entries in any column must be of the same kind.", "optc": "The columns must be ordered.", "optd": "No two rows in a table may be identical.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "For some relations, changing the data can have undesirable consequences called:", "opta": "referential integrity constraints.", "optb": "modification anomalies.", "optc": "normal forms.", "optd": "transitive dependencies.", "ans": "B", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A key:", "opta": "must always be composed of two or more columns.", "optb": "can only be one column.", "optc": "identifies a row.", "optd": "identifies a column.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "An attribute is a(n):", "opta": "column of a table.", "optb": "two dimensional table.", "optc": "row of a table.", "optd": "key of a table.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A relation in this form is free of all modification anomalies.", "opta": "First normal form", "optb": "Second normal form", "optc": "Third normal form", "optd": "Domain/key normal form", "ans": "D", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If attributes A and B determine attribute C, then it is also true that:", "opta": "A \u2192 C.", "optb": "B \u2192 C.", "optc": "(A,B) is a composite determinant.", "optd": "C is a determinant.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "A tuple is a(n):", "opta": "column of a table.", "optb": "two dimensional table.", "optc": "row of a table.", "optd": "key of a table.", "ans": "C", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "If attribute A determines both attributes B and C, then it is also true that:", "opta": "A \u2192 B.", "optb": "B \u2192 A.", "optc": "C \u2192 A.", "optd": "(B,C) \u2192 A.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}, {"question": "One solution to the multivalued dependency constraint problem is to:", "opta": "split the relation into two relations, each with a single theme.", "optb": "change the theme.", "optc": "create a new theme.", "optd": "add a composite key.", "ans": "A", "explanation": "No answer description available for this question. Let us discuss."}]]}